Skin is a drama, crime, history film directed by Guy Nattiv.
A destitute young man, raised by racist skinheads and notorious among white supremacists, turns his back on
hatred and violence to transform his life, with the help of a black activist and the woman he loves.
Bryon Widner, played by Jamie Bell.
Julie Price, played by Danielle Macdonald.
Shareen, played by Vera Farmiga.
Fred 'Hammer' Krager, played by Bill Camp.
April, played by Louisa Krause.
Desiree, played by Zoe Colletti.
Skin is a 2018 American biographical drama film
written and directed by Guy Nattiv.
The film stars Jamie Bell, Danielle Macdonald, Daniel Henshall, Bill Camp, Louisa Krause,
Zoe Colletti, Kylie Rogers, Colbi Gannett, Mike Colter, and Vera Farmiga.
The film is inspired by and loosely based on the true story of an
American neo-Nazi skinhead named Bryon Widner.
Skin had its world premiere at the 2018 Toronto International Film Festival on September 8, 2018 and was
released on June 27, 2019 through DirecTV Cinema before a wide release on July 26, 2019 by A24.
The tone is emotional.